<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<bylaws>
  <section>
    <number>Section 1</number>
    <title>Force and Effect</title>
    <content>1.1 These Bylaws bind the Strata Corporation and all owners/residents to the same extent, as if the Bylaws had been signed by the Strata Corporation, and each owner/resident and contained covenants on the part of the Strata Corporation with each owner/resident, and of each owner/resident with every other owner/resident to observe and perform every provision of these Bylaws.

1.2 All owners, residents and visitors must comply strictly with these Bylaws and the Rules of the Strata Corporation, as adopted and amended from time to time.</content>
    <part>PART 1</part>
    <partTitle>INTERPRETATION AND EFFECT</partTitle>
  </section>
  <section>
    <number>Section 2</number>
    <title>Payment of Strata Fees and Special Levies</title>
    <content>2.1 An owner must pay strata fees on or before the first (1st) day of the month to which the strata fees relate.

2.2 If an owner fails to pay the strata fees on time, the owner must pay interest on the arrears at the rate of 10% per annum, compounded annually, and calculated on a monthly basis from the date the payment was due until the date of payment.</content>
    <part>PART 2</part>
    <partTitle>DUTIES OF OWNERS, TENANTS, OCCUPANTS AND VISITORS</partTitle>
  </section>
  <section>
    <number>Section 3</number>
    <title>Use of Property</title>
    <content>3.1 An owner, tenant, occupant or visitor must not use a strata lot, the common property or limited common property in a way that causes unreasonable noise, causes a nuisance or hazard to another person, interferes unreasonably with the rights of other persons to use and enjoy the common property, limited common property or another strata lot, is illegal, or is not in compliance with the purpose for which the strata lot is to be used as shown in the Form V filed in the Land Title Office.</content>
    <part>PART 2</part>
    <partTitle>DUTIES OF OWNERS, TENANTS, OCCUPANTS AND VISITORS</partTitle>
  </section>
</bylaws> 